How long before I get in?
Before it starts, before I begin
How long before you decide
But before I know what it feels like
Where to, where do I go?
If you never tried then you'll never know
How long do I have to climb
Up on the side of this mountain of mine
Look up, I look up at night
Planets are moving at the speed of light
Climb up, up in the trees Every chance that you get is a chance you seize
How long am I gonna stand When my head's stuck under the sand
I'll stop before I can stop Or before I see things the right way up
All that noise and all that sound
All those places I got found
Birds go flying at the speed of sound
Until I show you how it all began
Birds can fly from the underground
If you could see it then you'd understand
Ideas that you'll never find
All the inventors can never design
The buildings that you put up
What you build and shine are all made up
A sign that I couldn't read
Or a light that I couldn't see
Some things you have to believe
But others are puzzles, puzzle and room
All that noise and all that sound
All those places I got from
Birds got flying at the speed of sound
To show you how it all began
Birds came flying from behind the ground
If you could see it then you'd understand
Oh, when you see it then you'll understand
All those signs, tell me what they meant
Some things you can't invent
Some get made and some get sent
Ooh, the birds go flying at the speed of sound
To show you how it all began
Birds keep flying from the underground
If you can see it then you'll understand
Oh, when we see it then you'll understand