shh, quiet
today I don't feel like doing anything
I just wanna lay in my bed
Don't feel like picking up my phone
So leave a message at the tone
Cause today I swear I'm not doing anything
I'm gonna kick my feet up and stare at the fan
Turn the TV on, throw my hand in my pants
Nobody's gonna tell me I can't
Nah, I'll be lounging on the couch just chilling in my Snuggie
Click to MTV so they can teach me how to dougie
Cause in my castle I'm the freaking man
Oh yes I said it, I said it, I said it cause I can
Today I don't feel like doing anything
I just wanna lay in my bed
Don't feel like picking up my phone
So leave a message at the tone
Cause today I swear I'm not doing anything
Nothing at all
Woohoo, woohoo, woohoo
Tomorrow I'll wake up, do some P90X Meet a really nice girl, have some really nice
sex And she's gonna scream out, this is great
Oh my god, this is great Yeah, I might mess around and give my college
degree I bet my old man will be so proud of me
But sorry pops, you'll just have to wait Oh yes, I said it, I said it, I said it
Today I don't feel like doing anything I just wanna lay in my bed
Don't feel like picking up my phone So leave a message at the tone
Cause today I swear I'm not doing anything No, I ain't gonna comb my hair
Cause I ain't going anywhere
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I'll just strut in my birthday suit
And let everything hang loose
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, today I don't feel like doing anything
I just wanna lay in my bed
Don't feel like picking up my phone
So leave a message at the tone
Cause today I swear I'm not doing anything
Nothing at all
Woo hoo, woo hoo, ooh