Remember, always love you, bye!
I just wanted you to know that baby you're the best
I got my red dress on tonight
Dancing in the dark in the pale moonlight
Throw my hair up real big, beauty queen style
High heels off, I'm feeling alive
Oh my god, I feel it in the air
Telephone wires above are sizzling like a snare
Honey, I'm, I'm fine, I feel it everywhere
Nothing scares me anymore
Kiss me hard before you go
Summertime suddenly
I just wanted you to know
That the day will come
I got that summertime, summertime sadness
S-s-summertime, summertime sadness
Got that summertime, summertime sadness
Oh, oh, oh
I'm feeling electric tonight
Cruising down the coast, going about 99
I'm a bad baby by my heavenly side. I know if I go I die happy
I'm happy tonight
Oh my god
I feel it in the air
Tell her from miles above
All sizzling like a snare
Honey I'm, I'm fine
I feel it everywhere
Nothing scares me anymore
Kiss me hard before you go
Summer time silence
I just wanted you to know, baby, you missed me.
I got that summertime, summertime sadness.
Got that summertime, summertime sadness.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Think I'll miss you forever
Like the stars meet the sun in the morning sky
Late is better than never
Even if you're gone, I'm gonna try
Try
I got that summertime, summertime sadness
Summertime, summertime sadness
Got that summertime, summertime sadness
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Kiss me hard before you go
Summertime sadness
I just wanted you to know
You