Oh, I'm okay. I will be.
I said she could stay with us, Mum. I just thought she feels better.
Yeah, of course she can.
Oh, this won't be for long.
Well, you can stay as long as you want, my love.
You really missed you.
Pops.
Great to see you, love.
Oh.
All right, shall we get you off to bed, then?
You should have given me some room
and I'd have put the electric blanket on.
Sorry. All right, Della.
Freeze.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
All right, then.
Freeze them up there.
In a bedroom, Peter unpacks her suitcase.
The middle-aged woman opens her green case.
Do you want, yeah, PJs?
Yeah.
Lifting a bundle of pajamas,
Peter finds a sheet of paper labeled
Lancaster North Hospital Discharged Sheet.
He closes the suitcase and brings glory to the pajamas.
There you go.
Thank you.
He picks up the locket.
You kept it.
Oh, of course.